hey Blake I'm feeling sick so I need you
to work my desk for the rest of the day
you look
horrible yeah about that I can't not
today Cota Ronin comes out tonight and I
got to save a spot in line at the video
game store actually I was just about to
leave check it
out it's good for him huh I'm going to
put him in the bathroom stall tell
everybody I'm crapping the rest of the
day okay well I can't lie to you guys
I'm not really sick I just I told Alice
that so I could leave early to go see
Walking with Dinosaurs Arena spectacular
uh maybe one of these guys could cover
for you I really shouldn't it would set
a precedence in this office that we
don't need no for Alice we'd probably
end up fugging all day getting no work
done please Blake I mean my lifelong
dream is to live in Jurassic Park times
1993 please I really need this I need it
okay please blame all right all right
all right okay great yeah that's Alice's
appointment book okay sure appointment b
a lot of fun out of here Julian feel
better oh no I'm not actually sick so
what you said about my face earlier was
that was
rude